gta5cheats.com 2019-09-23

# Privacy Policy - GTA BOOM

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or via our app, fill out a form, or make a comment on an article.

You may, however, visit our site or use our app anonymously.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available [here](https://automattic.com/privacy/). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Contact Form Submissions

If you choose to email us, we retain the email address provided and any other details provided by you in order to respond to you, should it be necessary. We do not use any information submitted via the contact form for marketing purposes.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  2. To improve our website and/or our app (we continually strive to improve our website and application offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  3. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site and/or app feature
  4. To attempt to show you advertisements that are most relevant or helpful to you

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information, including SHA-256 secure browser encryption.

## Do we use cookies?

If you allow, yes (cookies are small files that a site, app or its respective service provider(s) transfer to your device's hard drive (if you allow) that enables the sites, apps or service providers systems to recognize your device and capture and remember certain information).

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site and app traffic and site and app interaction, so that we can offer better site and app experiences and tools in the future.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

## Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you may request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You may also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site or app policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

## Partners

Certain partners have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from our website users in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer.

## Advertising Affiliations

GTA BOOM is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC ( **AdThrive** ) for the purposes of placing advertising on our site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on our site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using GTA BOOM, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative's multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

### For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us using [this form](https://www.gtaboom.com/contact/) and contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com.

## Amazon Affiliate Program

GTA BOOM is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com. Amazon offers a small commission on products sold via their affiliate links and each of the purchase you make via our Amazon affiliate links supports our site at no cost to you.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website or in our app. These third party offerings have separate and independent privacy policies. We have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked offerings. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and our app, and welcome any feedback about these offerings.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit GTA BOOM or use GTA 5 Cheater (our app). These companies may use aggregated information about your visits to this and other websites, and your use of our app, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## European Union Citizens

Despite any other section of this document, this site is not targeted towards citizens of the European Union. If you visit or use this website in any way whatsoever, you are agreeing and confirming you are not a citizen of the European Union.

## Your Consent

By using our site or our app, you consent to our online privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on October 23, 2018.
